Class of 1902 Records, 1898-1967
Smith College Archives
Class of 1902 Records
1898-1967
Smith College. Class of 1902.
RG 80 UUID:2e49794b-6e08-4f35-8fad-28f106198248
20 boxes (11 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 20 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1902.
The Class of 1902 was the twenty-fourth entering class and the twenty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1902 records, 1898-1967, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1902, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, financial information, and other memorabilia. The Class of 1902 records also includes a necrology from the Class Secretary's notes.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1902 records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class animal undated (Box 1613, Folder 1)
- Baccalaureate Service 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 3)
- Commencement Music 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 4)
- Commencement Photos 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 5)
- Commencement Speaker 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 6)
- Freshman Handbook 1898 (Box 1613, Folder 7)
- Freshman Grind 1898 (Box 1613, Folder 8)
- Fund Letters 1905-1964 (Box 1613, Folder 9)
- Groups 1898-1902 (Box 1613, Folder 10)
- Groups 1898-1902 (Box 1613, Folder 11)
- History undated (Box 1613, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day Photos 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 14)
- Junior-Senior Dance 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 15)
- Junior Frolic 1901 (Box 1613, Folder 16)
- Junior Prom 1901 (Box 1613, Folder 17)
- Class Letters 1910-1962 (Box 1613, Folder 18)
- Memorial Gifts 1919-1929 (Box 1613, Folder 19)
- Organization undated (Box 1613, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1903-1910 (Box 1614, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1910-1920 (Box 1614, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1920-1930 (Box 1614, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1931-1935 (Box 1614, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1937 (Box 1614, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 1614, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1947 (Box 1614, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1950-1955 (Box 1614, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 1614, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1962, 1967 (Box 1614, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 1614, Folder 11)
- Reunions undated (Box 1614, Folder 12)
- Senior Dramatics, script 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics- Photos 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 5)
- Scholarships undated (Box 1615, Folder 6)
- Sophomore Reception 1898-1899 (Box 1615, Folder 7)
- Songs, General undated (Box 1615, Folder 8)
- Class Supper 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 9)
- Class of 1902- Class Secretary's Records: Necrology
  - Class Secretary's Notes: Necrology (Box 1616, Folder 1)
  - Barnes, Blanche Elizabeth (Box 1616, Folder 2)
  - Brown, Edith Werner (Box 1616, Folder 3)
  - Crandall, Leona (Box 1616, Folder 4)
  - Demond, Anna Louise (Box 1616, Folder 5)
  - Dowling, Florence Louise (Box 1616, Folder 6)
  - Drake, Harriet Frances (Box 1616, Folder 7)
  - Edwardes, Ethellone (Box 1616, Folder 8)
  - Ely, Edith Goodhue (Box 1616, Folder 9)
  - Goss, Stella Elizabeth (Box 1616, Folder 10)
  - Holden, Bertha Haynes (Box 1616, Folder 11)
  - McLellane, Myra (Box 1616, Folder 12)
  - McClure, Anna Margaret (Box 1616, Folder 13)
  - Montgomery, Beatrice (Box 1616, Folder 14)
  - Peirce, Marda (Box 1616, Folder 15)
  - Perkins, Louise Childs (Box 1616, Folder 16)
  - Rogers, Laura Mary (Box 1616, Folder 17)
  - Thalheimer, Ethel Seymour (Box 1616, Folder 18)
  - Westcott, Laura Johnson (Box 1616, Folder 19)
  - Wicker, Lucy Southwort (Box 1616, Folder 20)
  - Burbeck, Bertha May (Box 1616, Folder 21)
  - Butler, Mary Lucretia (Box 1616, Folder 22)
- Reunion Scrapbook (Box OV)